<exptext>
  <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>Blank</title>
    <explanation>
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>

  <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <explanation>
Welcome to the FemtoNET Explorer. We begin our journey floating in VERY SMALL SPACE. You'll notice that geometry gets a bit... wobbly down here, which is why our coordinate plane is shifting around like a mildly turbulent sea. Particles flit in and out of existence due to WEIRD QUANTUM WEIRDNESS. 

Press "Initialize" to begin.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>

  <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>Initialized</title>
    <explanation>
We load in an electron and, in the distance, a particle detector. (These are not simulated to scale-- in reality the detector is SIGNIFICANTLY larger; if the electron were a baseball, the detector would be the size of the earth.) 

Press "Launch" to send the electron into the detector.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>

  <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>FirstElectronFired</title>
    <explanation>
The electron fires into the detector and... something is detected. Let's follow it and see where it goes.

Check "Follow Particles" and then "Launch" another.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>
    <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>DriveByPhoton</title>
    <explanation>
When the electron is near to the proton, it releases a high-energy photon. The photon continues towards the proton, while the electron is deflected.

Click "Play" when you're ready to see the next step.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>
    <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>CollisionWithProton</title>
    <explanation>
The photon collides with the proton and the proton is both deflected and charged with energy from the photon. 

Click "Play" when you're ready to see the next step.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>
    <ParsedExplanationText>
    <title>SecondPhotonReleased</title>
    <explanation>
The proton releases a high-energy photon a few moments later to shed the excess energy. The proton and the high-energy photon are then both detected by the detector.

Click "Play" when you're ready to see the next step.
    </explanation>
  </ParsedExplanationText>
</exptext>